<odoo>
    <record id="9780765388971" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765388971.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765388971</field>
        <field name="title">The Consuming Fire</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Consuming Fire&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;—&lt;b&gt;the sequel to the 2018 Hugo Award Best Novel finalist and 2018 Locus Award-winning &lt;i&gt;The Collapsing Empire&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;—&lt;b&gt;an epic space-opera novel in the bestselling Interdependency series, from the Hugo Award-winning and &lt;i&gt;New York Times &lt;/i&gt;bestselling author John Scalzi&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Interdependency, humanity’s interstellar empire, is on the verge of collapse. The Flow, the extra-dimensional conduit that makes travel between the stars possible, is disappearing, leaving entire star systems stranded. When it goes, human civilization may go with it—unless desperate measures can be taken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emperox Grayland II, the leader of the Interdependency, is ready to take those measures to help ensure the survival of billions. But nothing is ever that easy. Arrayed before her are those who believe the collapse of the Flow is a myth—or at the very least, an opportunity that can allow them to ascend to power. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Grayland prepares for disaster, others are preparing for a civil war, a war that will take place in the halls of power, the markets of business and the altars of worship as much as it will take place between spaceships and battlefields. The Emperox and her allies are smart and resourceful, but then so are her enemies. Nothing about this power struggle will be simple or easy... and all of humanity will be caught in its widening gyre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Interdependency Series&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. &lt;i&gt;The Collapsing Empire&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2. &lt;i&gt;The Consuming Fire&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780553803723" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780553803723.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Isaac Asimov</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780553803723</field>
        <field name="title">Foundation and Empire</field>
        <field name="summary">"This mysterious entity possesses a force and stature beyond anything humany conceivable. But even more terrifying than its strength are the eyes it keeps hidden beyind impenetrable shades - eyes that are rumored to have the power of death. Who - or what - is the Mule? And how is humanity to defend itself against this invulnerable avatar of annihilation?"--BOOK JACKET.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780345453747" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780345453747.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Douglas Adams</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780345453747</field>
        <field name="title">The Ultimate Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;b&gt;At last in paperback in one complete volume, here are the five classic novels from Douglas Adams’s beloved Hitchiker series.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Seconds before the Earth is demolished for a galactic freeway, Arthur Dent is saved by Ford Prefect, a researcher for the revised &lt;i&gt;Guide&lt;/i&gt;. Together they stick out their thumbs to the stars and begin a wild journey through time and space.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Restaurant at the End of the Universe&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Facing annihilation at the hands of warmongers is a curious time to crave tea. It could only happen to the cosmically displaced Arthur Dent and his comrades as they hurtle across the galaxy in a desperate search for a place to eat.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Life, the Universe and Everything&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;The unhappy inhabitants of planet Krikkit are sick of looking at the night sky– so they plan to destroy it. The universe, that is. Now only five individuals can avert Armageddon: mild-mannered Arthur Dent and his stalwart crew.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;So Long, and Thanks for All the Fish&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Back on Earth, Arthur Dent is ready to believe that the past eight years were all just a figment of his stressed-out imagination. But a gift-wrapped fishbowl with a cryptic inscription conspires to thrust him back to reality. So to speak.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mostly Harmless&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Just when Arthur Dent makes the terrible mistake of starting to enjoy life, all hell breaks loose. Can he save the Earth from total obliteration? Can he save the &lt;i&gt;Guide&lt;/i&gt; from a hostile alien takeover? Can he save his daughter from herself?</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780553803716" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780553803716.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Isaac Asimov</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780553803716</field>
        <field name="title">Foundation</field>
        <field name="summary">One of the great masterworks of science fiction, the Foundation novels of Isaac Asimov are unsurpassed for their unique blend of nonstop action, daring ideas, and extensive world-building. The story of our future begins with the history of Foundation and its greatest psychohistorian: Hari Seldon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For twelve thousand years the Galactic Empire has ruled supreme. Now it is dying. Only Hari Seldon, creator of the revolutionary science of psychohistory, can see into the future—a dark age of ignorance, barbarism, and warfare that will last thirty thousand years. To preserve knowledge and save mankind, Seldon gathers the best minds in the Empire—both scientists and scholars—and brings them to &lt;br&gt;a bleak planet at the edge of the Galaxy to serve as a beacon of hope for future generations. He calls his sanctuary the Foundation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But soon the fledgling Foundation finds itself at the mercy of corrupt warlords rising in the wake of the receding Empire. And mankind's last best hope is faced with an agonizing choice: submit to the barbarians and live as slaves—or take a stand for freedom and risk total destruction.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780765316974" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765316974.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765316974</field>
        <field name="title">The Last Colony</field>
        <field name="summary">Retired from his fighting days, John Perry is now village ombudsman for a human colony on distant Huckleberry. With his wife, former Special Forces warrior Jane Sagan, he farms several acres, adjudicates local disputes, and enjoys watching his adopted daughter grow up.&lt;br&gt;That is, until his and Jane's past reaches out to bring them back into the game--as leaders of a new human colony, to be peopled by settlers from all the major human worlds, for a deep political purpose that will put Perry and Sagan back in the thick of interstellar politics, betrayal, and war.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780765354068" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765354068.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765354068</field>
        <field name="title">The Ghost Brigades</field>
        <field name="summary">The Ghost Brigades are the Special Forces of the Colonial Defense Forces, elite troops created from the DNA of the dead and turned into the perfect soldiers for the CDF's toughest operations. They’re young, they’re fast and strong, and they’re totally without normal human qualms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The universe is a dangerous place for humanity—and it's about to become far more dangerous. Three races that humans have clashed with before have allied to halt our expansion into space. Their linchpin: the turncoat military scientist Charles Boutin, who knows the CDF’s biggest military secrets. To prevail, the CDF must find out why Boutin did what he did. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Jared Dirac is the only human who can provide answers -- a superhuman hybrid, created from Boutin's DNA, Jared’s brain should be able to access Boutin's electronic memories. But when the memory transplant appears to fail, Jared is given to the Ghost Brigades. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; At first, Jared is a perfect soldier, but as Boutin’s memories slowly surface, Jared begins to intuit the reason’s for Boutin’s betrayal. As Jared desperately hunts for his "father," he must also come to grips with his own choices. Time is running out: The alliance is preparing its offensive, and some of them plan worse things than humanity’s mere military defeat... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "A mix of Starship Troopers and Universal Soldier, Ghost Brigades evokes awakening, betrayal, and combat in the best military sci-fi tradition."—Entertainment Weekly &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "An impressive piece of work."—Philadelphia Inquirer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "Fast and deep . . . I like the galaxy this author's playing in, the characters he limns, the situations he's playing with, and I'm glad there's at least one more volume on the way."—San Diego Union-Tribune &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "In Heinleinesque fashion, the book is loaded with scenes of comradeship, isolation, ruthlessness and the protocols, which govern the lives of active-duty soldiers. But this is where Scalzi, famous for his blog ‘The Whatever,’ surpasses Heinlein. Scalzi weaves in subtle discussions of humanity's growing fear of aging and our simultaneous attraction and repulsion to the Frankenstein-like creatures we are able to create."—San Antonio Express-News &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "Scalzi is a natural heir to Heinlein, and his second book in this series is a good old-fashioned space opera, which takes time to question the nature of free will."—St. Louis Press-Dispatch &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "The alliance of three alien races against interstellar humanity, the defection of a human military scientist, and the signs of an impending war call for desperate measures from the Colonial Defense Forces. The creation of the superhuman hybrid Jared Dirac from the DNA of the traitor Charles Boutin is intended to provide a window on Boutin's mind and on the reasons for the alien alliance, but the transfer apparently fails, and Dirac is assigned to the Ghost Brigades, Special Forces troops cloned from the DNA of dead men minus any moral qualms. The sequel to Old Man's War combines taut military action with keen insights into the moral issues revolving around developing technologies. Scalzi has a finely tuned sense of balance between personal drama and the ‘big picture’ in this SCI FI Essential Book choice. Highly recommended."—Library Journal (starred review) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "Scalzi's riveting and original Old Man's War introduced readers to the Colonial Defense Forces (CDF), an Earth-based galactic army composed of senior citizens rejuvenated by high-tech wizardry into youthful warriors. In this equally engaging, battle-driven sequel, the CDF's latest operation entails tracking down renegade scientist Charles Boutin, who is responsible for handing over deadly military secrets to humanity's extraterrestrial enemies. Fortunately, a computer-based replica of Boutin's consciousness is on file and ready for transfer into newly cloned special-forces soldier Jirad Dirac, who shares Boutin's DNA. When the consciousness transfer doesn't quite take, Dirac is handed off to a battalion for routine but closely monitored training. Just when Dirac is getting comfortable with his own identity, however, Boutin's memories kick in, and Dirac and his team are summarily dispatched to an enemy planet to capture Boutin and solve the mystery of his treason before humanity is destroyed. Scalzi skillfully weaves together action, memorable characterizations, and a touch of philosophy in a first-rate military sf outing."—Carl Hays, Booklist &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "[A] fast-paced interstellar military drama . . . It follows Jared Dirac, a superhuman soldier, from unusual birth to ambiguous death. Dirac is an altered clone of Charles Boutin, a military scientist who betrayed humankind to alien aggressors, and the Colonial Defense Forces' only hope of finding Boutin lies in transplanting his memories into Dirac's brain. When the transplant seems to fail, Dirac is sent to Special Forces, known as the Ghost Brigades for their habit of creating new soldiers from the DNA of the dead. His indoctrination there comes in handy when Boutin's memories begin to surface. Scalzi pays gleeful homage to Ender's Game, The Forever War and Starship Troopers."—Publishers Weekly</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780765316981" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765316981.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765316981</field>
        <field name="title">Zoe's Tale</field>
        <field name="summary">How do you tell your part in the biggest tale in history?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I ask because it's what I have to do. I'm Zoe Boutin Perry: A colonist stranded on a deadly pioneer world. Holy icon to a race of aliens. A player (and a pawn) in a interstellar chess match to save humanity, or to see it fall. Witness to history. Friend. Daughter. Human. Seventeen years old.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone on Earth knows the tale I am part of. But you don't know my tale: How I did what I did — how I did what I had to do — not just to stay alive but to keep you alive, too. All of you. I'm going to tell it to you now, the only way I know how: not straight but true, the whole thing, to try make you feel what I felt: the joy and terror and uncertainty, panic and wonder, despair and hope. Everything that happened, bringing us to Earth, and Earth out of its captivity. All through my eyes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a story you know. But you don't know it all.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780765376077" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765376077.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765376077</field>
        <field name="title">The End of All Things</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;p&gt;Hugo-award winning author, John Scalzi returns to his best-selling Old Man's War universe with &lt;i&gt;The End of All Things&lt;/i&gt;, the direct sequel to 2013's &lt;i&gt;The Human Division&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humans expanded into space...only to find a universe populated with multiple alien species bent on their destruction. Thus was the Colonial Union formed, to help protect us from a hostile universe. The Colonial Union used the Earth and its excess population for colonists and soldiers. It was a good arrangement...for the Colonial Union. Then the Earth said: no more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now the Colonial Union is living on borrowed time-a couple of decades at most, before the ranks of the Colonial Defense Forces are depleted and the struggling human colonies are vulnerable to the alien species who have been waiting for the first sign of weakness, to drive humanity to ruin. And there's another problem: A group, lurking in the darkness of space, playing human and alien against each other-and against their own kind -for their own unknown reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this collapsing universe, CDF Lieutenant Harry Wilson and the Colonial Union diplomats he works with race against the clock to discover who is behind attacks on the Union and on alien races, to seek peace with a suspicious, angry Earth, and keep humanity's union intact...or else risk oblivion, and extinction-and the end of all things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Man's War Series&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; #1 &lt;i&gt;Old Man’s War&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #2 &lt;i&gt;The Ghost Brigades&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #3 &lt;i&gt;The Last Colony&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #4 &lt;i&gt;Zoe’s Tale&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #5 &lt;i&gt;The Human Division&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #6 &lt;i&gt;The End of All Things &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; Short fiction: “After the Coup”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Other Tor Books&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Android’s Dream&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Agent to the Stars&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Your Hate Mail Will Be Graded&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Fuzzy Nation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Redshirts&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Lock In&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Collapsing Empire&lt;/i&gt; (forthcoming)&lt;/p&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780752224411" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780752224411.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Gail Herman</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780752224411</field>
        <field name="title">The Lost World</field>
        <field name="summary">Summer 1997 will see the release of Steven Spielberg's colossal new film The Lost World: Jurassic Park, the long awaited sequel to the unforgettable and highest grossing film of all time, Jurassic Park 'The Lost World: Jurassic Park Junior Novelisation' captures all the thrills and chills of The Lost World story, with heart-stopping suspense, hair-raising action and illustrated with colour photographs from the film.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780765316998" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780765316998.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765316998</field>
        <field name="title">Redshirts</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;p&gt;Ensign Andrew Dahl has just been assigned to the Universal Union Capital Ship &lt;i&gt;Intrepid&lt;/i&gt;, flagship of the Universal Union since the year 2456. It's a prestige posting, and Andrew is thrilled all the more to be assigned to the ship's Xenobiology laboratory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life couldn't be better...until Andrew begins to pick up on the fact that (1) every Away Mission involves some kind of lethal confrontation with alien forces, (2) the ship's captain, its chief science officer, and the handsome Lieutenant Kerensky always survive these confrontations, and (3) at least one low-ranked crew member is, sadly, always killed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not surprisingly, a great deal of energy below decks is expendedon avoiding, at all costs, being assigned to an Away Mission. Then Andrew stumbles on information that completely transforms his and his colleagues' understanding of what the starship &lt;i&gt;Intrepid &lt;/i&gt;really is...and offers them a crazy, high-risk chance to save their own lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Redshirts&lt;/i&gt; is the winner of the 2013 Hugo Award for Best Novel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Man's War Series&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; #1 &lt;i&gt;Old Man’s War&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #2 &lt;i&gt;The Ghost Brigades&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #3 &lt;i&gt;The Last Colony&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #4 &lt;i&gt;Zoe’s Tale&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #5 &lt;i&gt;The Human Division&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; #6 &lt;i&gt;The End of All Things &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; Short fiction: “After the Coup”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Other Tor Books&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Android’s Dream&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Agent to the Stars&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Your Hate Mail Will Be Graded&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Fuzzy Nation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Redshirts&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Lock In&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Collapsing Empire&lt;/i&gt; (forthcoming)&lt;/p&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9781596061033" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9781596061033.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9781596061033</field>
        <field name="title">The Sagan Diary</field>
        <field name="summary">Fans of John Scalzi's "Old Man" universe, prepare yourselves: there's a long new story in that universe, told from the point of view of one of the series' most intriguing characters. And for the first time, fans can become part of the universe themselves. Subterranean Press is proud to announce The Sagan Diary, a long novelette that for the first time looks at the worlds of the Hugo-nominated Old Man's War and its sequel The Ghost Brigades from the point of view of Lieutenant Jane Sagan, who in a series of diary entries gives her views on some of the events included in the series... and sheds new light into some previously unexplored corners. If you thought you knew Jane Sagan before, prepare to be surprised.</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9781444727333" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9781444727333.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Stephen King</field>
        <field name="isbn">9781444727333</field>
        <field name="title">11.22.63</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now a major TV series from JJ Abrams and Stephen King, starring James Franco (Hulu US, Fox UK and Europe, Stan Australia, SKY New Zealand).&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WHAT IF you could go back in time and change the course of history? WHAT IF the watershed moment you could change was the JFK assassination? 11.22.63, the date that Kennedy was shot - unless . . .&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;King takes his protagonist Jake Epping, a high school English teacher from Lisbon Falls, Maine, 2011, on a fascinating journey back to 1958 - from a world of mobile phones and iPods to a new world of Elvis and JFK, of Plymouth Fury cars and Lindy Hopping, of a troubled loner named Lee Harvey Oswald and a beautiful high school librarian named Sadie Dunhill, who becomes the love of Jake's life - a life that transgresses all the normal rules of time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With extraordinary imaginative power, King weaves the social, political and popular culture of his baby-boom American generation into a devastating exercise in escalating suspense.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780356502427" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780356502427.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Ann Leckie</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780356502427</field>
        <field name="title">Ancillary Mercy</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ancillary Mercy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;is the stunning conclusion to the trilogy that began with &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice&lt;/i&gt;, the only novel ever to win the Hugo, Nebula, and Arthur C. Clarke Awards.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For a moment, things seemed to be under control for Breq, the soldier who used to be a warship. Then a search of Athoek Station's slums turns up someone who shouldn't exist and a messenger from the mysterious Presger empire arrives, as does Breq's old enemy, the divided, heavily armed, and possibly insane Anaander Mianaai - ruler of an empire at war with itself.&lt;br&gt; Breq could flee with her ship and crew, but that would leave the people of Athoek in terrible danger. Breq has a desperate plan. The odds aren't good, but that's never stopped her before.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Imperial Radch trilogy begins with &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, continues in &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ancillary Sword&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and concludes with &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ancillary Mercy&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt; Also available now: &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Provenance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; is a stunning standalone adventure set in the same world as &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice. NPR&lt;/i&gt; calls it &lt;b&gt;'A fitting addition to the Ancillary world'&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Praise for the trilogy:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'ENGAGING AND PROVOCATIVE'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;SFX Magazine&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'UNEXPECTED, COMPELLING AND VERY COOL'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; John Scalzi&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'HIGHLY RECOMMENDED'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Independent on Sunday&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'MIND-BLOWING'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;io9.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'THRILLING, MOVING AND AWE-INSPIRING'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Guardian&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'UTTER PERFECTION'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Book Smugglers&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'ASTOUNDINGLY ASSURED AND GRACEFUL'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Strange Horizons&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;'ESTABLISHES LECKIE AS AN HEIR TO BANKS'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; Elizabeth Bear&lt;/p&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780316246651" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780316246651.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Ann Leckie</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780316246651</field>
        <field name="title">Ancillary Sword</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;b&gt;The sequel to &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice, &lt;/i&gt;the only novel to ever win the Hugo, Nebula, and Arthur C. Clarke Awards, and the second book in Ann Leckie's &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; bestselling series. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breq is a soldier who used to be a warship. Once a weapon of conquest controlling thousands of minds, now she has only a single body and serves the emperor.&lt;br&gt;With a new ship and a troublesome crew, Breq is ordered to go to the only place in the galaxy she would agree to go: to Athoek Station to protect the family of a lieutenant she once knew - a lieutenant she murdered in cold blood. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the Ancillary world: &lt;/b&gt;1. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice&lt;/i&gt;2. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Sword&lt;/i&gt;3. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Mercy&lt;/i&gt;</field>
    </record>
    <record id="9780316246620" model="library.book">
        <field file="library/static/img/9780316246620.jpg" name="image" type="base64" />
        <field name="author">Ann Leckie</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780316246620</field>
        <field name="title">Ancillary Justice</field>
        <field name="summary">&lt;b&gt;The only novel ever to win the Hugo, Nebula, and Arthur C. Clarke Awards and the first book in Ann Leckie's &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; bestselling trilogy. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;On a remote, icy planet, the soldier known as Breq is drawing closer to completing her quest.&lt;br&gt;Once, she was the Justice of Toren - a colossal starship with an artificial intelligence linking thousands of soldiers in the service of the Radch, the empire that conquered the galaxy. &lt;br&gt;Now, an act of treachery has ripped it all away, leaving her with one fragile human body, unanswered questions, and a burning desire for vengeance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the Ancillary world: &lt;/b&gt;1. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Justice&lt;/i&gt;2. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Sword&lt;/i&gt;3. &lt;i&gt;Ancillary Mercy&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;</field>
    </record>
</odoo>