<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_hh_1">
        <field name="title">The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy</field>
        <field name="author">Douglas Adams</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780345418913</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>Seconds before the Earth is demolished to make way for a galactic freeway,
            Arthur Dent is plucked off the planet by his friend Ford Prefect, a researcher
            for the revised edition of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy who, for the
            last fifteen years, has been posing as an out-of-work actor.</p>
            <p>Together this dynamic pair begin a journey through space aided by quotes from
            The Hitchhiker's Guide ("A towel is about the most massively useful thing an
            interstellar hitchhiker can have") and a galaxy-full of fellow travelers: Zaphod
            Beeblebrox—the two-headed, three-armed ex-hippie and totally out-to-lunch
            president of the galaxy; Trillian, Zaphod's girlfriend (formally Tricia McMillan),
            whom Arthur tried to pick up at a cocktail party once upon a time zone; Marvin,
            a paranoid, brilliant, and chronically depressed robot; Veet Voojagig, a former
            graduate student who is obsessed with the disappearance of all the ballpoint
            pens he bought over the years.</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/hitchhiker.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_hh_2">
        <field name="title">The Restaurant at the End of the Universe</field>
        <field name="author">Douglas Adams</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780345418920</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>Facing annihilation at the hands of the warlike Vogons is a curious time
            to have a cosmically displaced Arthur Dent and his curious comrades in arms
            as they hurtle through space powered by pure improbability - and desperately
            in search of a place to eat. Among Arthur's motley shipmates are Ford Prefect,
            a long-time friend and contributor to the The Hitch Hiker's Guide to the
            Galaxy; Zaphod Beeblebrox, the three-armed, two-headed ex-president of the
            galaxy; Tricia McMilan, a fellow Earth refuge who's gone native (her name is
            Trillian now); and Marvin, who suffers nothing and no one gladly.</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/hitchhiker_2.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_js_1">
        <field name="title">The Collapsing Empire</field>
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765388889</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>The first novel of a new space-opera sequence set in an all-new universe by the
            Hugo Award-winning, New York Times-bestselling author of Redshirts and
            Old Man's War.</p>
            <p>Our universe is ruled by physics and faster than light travel is not possible
            -- until the discovery of The Flow, an extra-dimensional field we can access
            at certain points in space-time that transport us to other worlds, around
            other stars.</p>
            <p>Humanity flows away from Earth, into space, and in time forgets our home
            world and creates a new empire, the Interdependency, whose ethos requires
            that no one human outpost can survive without the others. It’s a hedge
            against interstellar war -- and a system of control for the rulers of
            the empire.</p>
            <p>The Flow is eternal -- but it is not static. Just as a river changes
            course, The Flow changes as well, cutting off worlds from the rest of
            humanity. When it’s discovered that The Flow is moving, possibly cutting
            off all human worlds from faster than light travel forever, three individuals
            -- a scientist, a starship captain and the Empress of the Interdependency
            -- are in a race against time to discover what, if anything, can be salvaged
            from an interstellar empire on the brink of collapse. </p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/collapsing.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_js_2">
        <field name="title">The Consuming Fire</field>
        <field name="author">John Scalzi</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780765388971</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>The Interdependency, humanity’s interstellar empire, is on the verge of
            collapse. The Flow, the extra-dimensional conduit that makes travel between
            the stars possible, is disappearing, leaving entire star systems stranded.
            When it goes, human civilization may go with it—unless desperate measures
            can be taken.</p>

            <p>Emperox Grayland II, the leader of the Interdependency, is ready to take
            those measures to help ensure the survival of billions. But nothing is ever
            that easy. Arrayed before her are those who believe the collapse of the Flow
            is a myth—or at the very least, an opportunity that can allow them to ascend
            to power.</p>

            <p>While Grayland prepares for disaster, others are preparing for a civil war,
            a war that will take place in the halls of power, the markets of business and
            the altars of worship as much as it will take place between spaceships and
            battlefields. The Emperox and her allies are smart and resourceful, but then
            so are her enemies. Nothing about this power struggle will be simple or easy...
            and all of humanity will be caught in its widening gyre.</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/collapsing_2.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_jp_1">
        <field name="title">Jurassic Park</field>
        <field name="author">Michael Crichton</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780784838068</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>An astonishing technique for recovering and cloning dinosaur DNA has
            been discovered. Now humankind’s most thrilling fantasies have come true.
            Creatures extinct for eons roam Jurassic Park with their awesome presence
            and profound mystery, and all the world can visit them—for a price.
            Until something goes wrong...</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/jurassic.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_jp_2">
        <field name="title">The Lost World</field>
        <field name="author">Michael Crichton</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780752224411</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>It is now six years since the secret disaster at Jurassic Park, six years
            since the extraordinary dream of science and imagination came to a crashing
            end – the dinosaurs destroyed, the park dismantled, the island indefinitely
            closed to the public.</p>

            <p>There are rumors that something has survived....</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/jurassic_2.jpg"/>
    </record>

    <record model="library.book" id="book_demo_4">
        <field name="title">The Martian</field>
        <field name="author">Andy Weir</field>
        <field name="isbn">9780804139021</field>
        <field name="summary">
            <![CDATA[
            <p>Six days ago, astronaut Mark Watney became one of the first people
            to walk on Mars.</p>
            <p>Now, he’s sure he’ll be the first person to die there.</p>
            <p>After a dust storm nearly kills him and forces his crew to evacuate
            while thinking him dead, Mark finds himself stranded and completely
            alone with no way to even signal Earth that he’s alive—and even if
            he could get word out, his supplies would be gone long before a rescue
            could arrive.</p>
            <p>Chances are, though, he won’t have time to starve to death. The
            damaged machinery, unforgiving environment, or plain-old “human error”
            are much more likely to kill him first.</p>
            <p>But Mark isn’t ready to give up yet. Drawing on his ingenuity,
            his engineering skills — and a relentless, dogged refusal to quit
            — he steadfastly confronts one seemingly insurmountable obstacle
            after the next. Will his resourcefulness be enough to overcome the
            impossible odds against him?</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="image" type="base64" file="library/static/img/martian.jpg"/>
    </record>

</odoo>
